I received a black envelope last night.
We didn't return to reality at all.
This is still a system instance.
I got one too.
What does it say?
Keep an absolutely happy smile.
Listen,
the rule of this instance is that
no negative emotions are allowed.
No sadness, fear, or pain.
If you show even a little bit,
it will trigger the system,
and monsters will purge you into an NPC
that only knows how to smile.
From now on,
Qiqi and Chubby, you two stay together
and monitor each other's emotions.
Xiaofei, you're in charge of
recording all anomalies.
We must find the server terminal
of this world.
Han,
what about Yang?
Why isn't he here?
Don't contact him for now.
Why? Isn't Yang one of us?
He's too adapted to this perfect world.
Until we find out if he's controlled
by the system,
he's an extremely dangerous
potential risk.
Why are you here in the middle
of the night?
I can't sleep alone.
Whenever I close my eyes,
all I see are the monsters and blood
from the instances.
Can I stay here for a while?
Come in. You can rest here.
I'll go heat up some milk for you.
Warning.
Illegal access.
Core data offline.
Cleaners dispatched.
Mr. Liu Yiyang,
in the past four instances,
your combat data,
emotional data, and decision-making models
have interested me very much.
You have an extremely strong desire
to protect,
even a self-destructive one.
Cut the crap. What do you want?
I need someone with a strong desire
to protect
to help me maintain the operation
of the fifth instance.
You can become the administrator
of this new world.
In return,
your friends will never be hurt,
afraid,
or bleed again.
There are no monsters
and no death here.
What's the price?
The price is that
you will bear all the pain
of this world alone.
Whenever someone has abnormal emotions,
you need to act as the administrator
and cooperate with me to recycle
their pain onto yourself.
He's stubborn.
If he finds out,
he will never forgive me.
He won't find out.
In my world,
they will only have perfect happiness.
Deal.
As long as they can live,
I don't care.
Liu Yiyang,
you idiot.